<html display_name="Prerequisites" linenum="59" tex_filename="./block0/about.tex">
  <p>
    <h2>Prerequisites</h2>
  </p>
  <p>
This is listed as an intermediate-level course. This is not because there are many mathematical prerequisites.[mathjaxinline]^*[/mathjaxinline] Rather, it is because this is primarily <span style="color:#99182C"><b class="bf">not</b></span> a computational course (although you will learn how to do some computations); learning this subject is not principally about acquiring computational ability, but is more a matter of fluency in its language and theory. You will have to think conceptually and theoretically about how all of these ideas fit together! </p>
  <p>
([mathjaxinline]^*[/mathjaxinline]: Every so often there will be some videos or questions which require some basic single-variable calculus, since there are nice examples and applications that use it. However, it will be possible to pass this course with no knowledge of calculus whatsoever. Other than that, the only mathematical prerequisite is high-school algebra.) </p>
  <p>
    <h2>Honor Code</h2>
  </p>
  <p>
Students are expected to abide by the EdX Honor Code Pledge. </p>
  <p>
By enrolling in an edX course or program, I agree that I will: </p>
  <ul class="itemize">
    <li>
      <p>
Complete all tests and assignments on my own, unless collaboration on an assignment is explicitly permitted. </p>
    </li>
    <li>
      <p>
Maintain only one user account and not let anyone else use my username and/or password. </p>
    </li>
    <li>
      <p>
Not engage in any activity that would dishonestly improve my results, or improve or hurt the results of others. </p>
    </li>
    <li>
      <p>
Not post answers to problems that are being used to assess learner performance. </p>
    </li>
  </ul>
  <p>
Students also may not use outside resources (looking up answers outside of the EdX course materials, using calculator or computer assistance) unless explicitly allowed. Initially, no computer/calculator assistance outside of basic arithmetic functions is allowed. Later on, this will be relaxed, and students will receive notice that certain additional tools are allowable. </p>
</html>
